<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Lifehacks on Bliss</title>
    <link>https://anic1618.github.io/lifehacks/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Lifehacks on Bliss</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 07 Oct 2022 23:15:01 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://anic1618.github.io/lifehacks/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Overthinking</title>
      <link>https://anic1618.github.io/lifehacks/overthinking/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Oct 2022 23:15:01 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anic1618.github.io/lifehacks/overthinking/</guid>
      <description>src: https://psyche.co/guides/how-to-stop-overthinking-with-help-from-metacognitive-strategies
Many people who, in trying to find answers or meaning, or in attempting to make the right decision, spend most of their waking hours scrutinising their minds for solutions. Ironically, in this process of trying to figure out how to proceed in life, they come to a standstill.
When we spend too much time analysing our problems and dilemmas, we often end up more at a loss than we were to begin with.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Competitiveness</title>
      <link>https://anic1618.github.io/lifehacks/competitiveness/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Oct 2022 22:40:02 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anic1618.github.io/lifehacks/competitiveness/</guid>
      <description>Competitiveness isn’t inherently good or bad, It can be motivating, encourage people to push themselves, expand their capacities and capabilities, and perform at a high level. Where it’s bad is where we compete in ways that are bad for other people.
If winning the competition becomes the ultimate goal you may be willing to sacrifice things along the way that could be very bad.
As per Psychology, we found that hypercompetitive individuals — those who have a need to win at all cost — were more impatient and irritable than their less-competitive counterparts and had higher self-reported health problems, including heart disease.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
